[
    {
        "question": "Which of your five senses tell you if something is hot or cold?",
        "choice1": "Touch",
        "choice2": "Smell",
        "choice3": "Taste",
        "choice4": "See",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question":
            " What animal goes “Moo”",
            "choice1": "Cat",
        "choice2": "Elephant",
        "choice3": "Bird",
        "choice4": "Cow",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question":
            " During which festival does Santa come to visit?",
            "choice1": "Halloween",
        "choice2": "Ganesh Chaturdhi",
        "choice3": "Christmas",
        "choice4": "New Year",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question":
            "Which among is the name of a Dinosaur living on land ?",
            "choice1": "Crabs",
        "choice2": "Tyrannosaurus ",
        "choice3": "Flemingo",
        "choice4": "Stegosaurus",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question":
            " In the nursery rhyme 'Jack and Jill', what do Jack and Jill go up the hill to fetch?",
            "choice1": "Jacks watch",
        "choice2": "To find his mom",
        "choice3": "A pail of water",
        "choice4": "To watch sunset",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question":
            " What animal is pink and has a curly tail?",
            "choice1":"Elephant",
        "choice2": "cat",
        "choice3": "Bear",
        "choice4": "Pig",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question":
            " What animal goes “quack quack”",
        "choice1": "Cat",
        "choice2": "Duck",
        "choice3": "Bird",
        "choice4": "Cow",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question":
            "What is 10-2?",
        "choice1": "12",
        "choice2": "8",
        "choice3": "2",
        "choice4": "10",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question":
            " What is 5+22?",
        "choice1": "25",
        "choice2": "26",
        "choice3": "27",
        "choice4": "28",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": " If you have a bowl with six apples and you take away four, how many do you have?",
        "choice1": "2",
        "choice2": "0;",
        "choice3": "4",
        "choice4": "6",
        "answer": 3
    }
]